<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:42:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pomona</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/pomona/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:42:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/pomona/</guid><description>The problem with resource allocation # Extreme levels of inequality in our society, exploding climate crisis and interrupted supply chains testify to the claim that our economy is broken. Markets are not distributing products and services in a way that would be beneficial for the society as a whole. Instead they appear to be skewed to benefiting certain minorities. Markets have also not succeeded in guaranteeing sufficient supply of essential public goods such as health care and education.</description></item><item><title>White Deer</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/white-deer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 17:41:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/white-deer/</guid><description>The problem with the “new” # Thinking about the future is an activity vital to human life. Ideas about what we think might or should happen in the future are a key input into decisions we make in the present. We engage in future thinking continuously, as individuals and as society. At the individual level, it often takes place without any effort, subconsciously, in dreaming, or during the daylight, in daydreaming.</description></item><item><title>The Garden of AI</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/garden-ai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 07:25:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/garden-ai/</guid><description>The problem with artificial intelligence # Agriculture started 12,000 ago when humans understood that a wonder of nature &amp;ndash; plant growth &amp;ndash; could be harnessed to their advantage. Many centuries later, humans are slowly understanding that another natural phenomenon, cognition, can similarly be &amp;lsquo;grown&amp;rsquo; and used to benefit work and social processes. Simulating cognition is the promise of Artificial Intelligence.
Unlike agriculture, though, the practice of AI is currently reserved to a handful of the world&amp;rsquo;s population.</description></item><item><title>Toppix</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/toppix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 07:23:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/toppix/</guid><description>The problem with recommender systems # The ability to provide recommendations is the common denominator of all large Internet companies. Whether their suggestions involve books, movies, washing machines, friends, or simply Web pages, the likelihood that they will retain their audience is correlated with the quality of their recommendation engine.
Typically, recommendation happens in a silo (Amazon does not recommend Netflix and vice versa). It also relies on algorithms that are often privacy-damaging and based on dubious principles (for instance, the idea that if you are friend with someone, you will like the same movies).</description></item><item><title>Fundamental research</title><link>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/research/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 11:41:45 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ninaris90.github.io/projects/research/</guid><description>Our company is named after a core concept in linguistics. In the subfield of semantics, a possible world is a formal object [&amp;hellip;]
Integration with formal semantics # There is currently a fierce debate in the AI community, surrounding the necessity for symbolic approaches to be integrated in large neural networks.
Integration with cognitive neuroscience # Building small AI requires a good understanding of the dimensionality in which human thoughts live.</description></item></channel></rss>