<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Possible Worlds on</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Possible Worlds on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2022 Possible Worlds</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://possible-words.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Science</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 09:25:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/science/</guid><description>It is our strong belief that the AI of the future will be based on science, rather than ad-hoc methods. We strive to simulate the most precious aspects of human cognition: the ability to explain, understand and imagine. Our strategy is to combine cutting-edge research in cognitive science and computational modelling to develop new types of algorithms. We build technologies that, we hope, might one day erase the gap between minds and machines.</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/team/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 12:42:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/team/</guid><description>Nina Rismal Nina is an economist and political philosopher interested in social change. She studied at SOAS, Oxford, and Cambridge, where she wrote her doctoral dissertation in defence of utopias. Since 2018 Nina has been based in Germany, working for research institutions and think tanks that focus on climate change and economic transformation. Aurelie Herbelot Aurelie has over 15 years experience in AI research.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:51:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/about/</guid><description>At Possible Worlds, we believe in the power of AI to enhance human creativity. Our mission is to build systems that support innovation in all corners of society. We strive to empower small businesses and creators. We also provide policy-makers with tools to imagine different futures. To achieve our goal, we actively integrate AI research and development with insights from social science, politics and the arts. We dream of a world where the world can truly be reinvented, and where technology supports the fundamental human drive for change.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://possible-words.xyz/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://possible-words.xyz/contact/</guid><description>For any enquiry about Possible Worlds, please contact Nina at:
user="nina",domain="possible-worlds.xyz",document.write(user+"@"+domain);nina at possible-worlds.xyz</description></item></channel></rss>